[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 1 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "13",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "14",
        "13",
        "12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 1 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "8",
        "5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 7 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "16",
        "13",
        "15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 4 \u00d7 1) \u00f7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "1",
        "0",
        "2"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 7 \u00d7 6) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "44",
      "options": [
        "43",
        "44",
        "45",
        "46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 3 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "34",
      "options": [
        "36",
        "34",
        "33",
        "35"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 3 \u00d7 2) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "7",
        "9",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 10 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "32",
      "options": [
        "34",
        "31",
        "32",
        "33"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 2 \u00d7 8) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 1 \u00d7 3) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "13",
        "11",
        "14"
      ]
    }
]